{
  "content": {
    "trivia": {
      "easy": {
	"ace": [
	  {
	    "id": "309fc142-dfac-4af9-bce8-c83d14d0dabf",
	    "question": "Who did ace wanted to avenge so badly that he went to confront Marshall D. Teach aka Blackbeard ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Thatch, the 4th division commander of the Whitebeard pirates",
	      "Jozu, the 3rd division commander of the Whitebeard pirates",
	      "Gol D. Roger, his deceased father and The Pirate King",
	      "Jimbe, former warlord and knight of the sea"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#78533a",
	    "answer": 0
	  }
	],
	"arlong": [
	  {
	    "id": "d4d37de1-5b4c-4e64-9783-1f4f87667503",
	    "question": "Which crew was Arlong a member of before becoming the captain of the Arlong Pirates ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Hody Pirates",
	      "Fishman Pirates",
	      "Roger Pirates",
	      "Sun Pirates"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#525971",
	    "answer": 3 
	  }
	],
	"bentham": [
	  {
	    "id": "47ce6c2b-39c6-4ce3-8a5f-fd2df6fe3b7c",
	    "question": "By what name was Bentham of the Wild referred to while serving as a member of Baroque Works ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Mr. 1",
	      "Mr. 2",
	      "Mr. 3",
	      "Mr. 4"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#d894ad",
	    "answer": 1
	  }
	],
	"brook": [
	  {
	    "id":"46dd977d-67a5-449d-b18b-e814bcffd012",
	    "question": "What is the name of Brook's former pirate crew ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Bumbar Pirates",
	      "Rumbar Pirates",
	      "Lumbar Pirates",
	      "Dumbar Pirates"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#695351",
	    "answer": 1
	  }
	],
	"crocodile": [
	  {
	    "id": "c48c229c-6362-424e-a4c1-3f16a92ee2db",
	    "question": "How many times did crocodile defeat luffy before finally succumbing to the might of our future pirate king ?",
	    "options": [
	      "One time",
	      "Two times",
	      "Three times",
	      "Four times"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#404744",
	    "answer": 1
	  }
	],
	"fujitora": [
	  {
	  
	    "id": "46dba3f3-ba3c-46e9-8b40-04388b4b4a93",
	    "question": "Navy Admiral Fujitora's devil fruit allows him to control which of the following ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Gravity",
	      "Wind",
	      "Shockwaves",
	      "Water"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#937cb1",
	    "answer": 0
	  }
	],
	"hancock": [
	  {
	    "id": "165f69f0-f838-48b8-8a2d-90759836fda5",
	    "question": "Boa Hancock is the pirate empress of which island kingdom ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Alabasta Kingdom",
	      "Kamabakka Kingdom",
	      "Amazon Lilly",
	      "Dressrosa"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#974554",
	    "answer": 2
	  }
	],
	"lucci": [
	  {
	    "id": "4cbb3c9b-3a35-4b76-ac9d-0d98fbf51281",
	    "question": "What is the name of the pigeon that is always seen perched on Rob Lucci's shoulder ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Hatori",
	      "Ratori",
	      "Satori",
	      "Datori"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#464646",
	    "answer": 0
	  }
	],
	"luffy": [
	  {
	    "id": "a8a09390-f6d2-4be1-ae44-fd0c62f897f0",
	    "question": "At what age did Luffy set out to sea ?",
	    "options": [
	      "15 years old",
	      "18 years old",
	      "16 years old",
	      "17 years old"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#a62724",
	    "answer": 3
	  }
	],
	"mihawk": [
	  {
	    "id": "47d5dfc8-01b5-49a8-b605-bcc642c41da8",
	    "question": "What is the name of Mihawk's sword ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Murakumogiri",
	      "Enma",
	      "Yoru",
	      "Shigure"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#8d505d",
	    "answer": 2
	  }
	],
	"robin": [
	  {
	    "id": "19f8df37-620f-4e56-a71d-d48d4d4335c5",
	    "question": "At what age did Nico Robin join the Strawhat crew ?",
	    "options": [
	      "27 years old",
	      "28 years old",
	      "29 years old",
	      "30 years old"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail",
	    "color": "#625d86",
	    "answer": 1
	  }
	],
	"sanji": [
	  {
	    "id": "f2e46a8e-0d4c-494f-85e1-342cc8048412",
	    "question": "What martial art does sanji employ as his signature fighting style ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Red Leg Style",
	      "Two Leg Style",
	      "Black Leg Style",
	      "Only Leg Style"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#4d4d4d",
	    "answer": 2
	  }
	],
	"sengoku": [
	  {
	    "id": "ff7a45dc-8d92-450a-aeb2-d648c8719e29",
	    "question": "Which admiral did former fleet admiral Sengoku favour as his successor ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Akainu",
	      "Aokiji",
	      "Kizaru",
	      "Fujitora"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#60547a",
	    "answer": 1
	  }
	],
	"smoker": [
	  {
	    "id": "ba42d2dd-0d18-4f69-a5ba-15592aea46eb",
	    "question": "On which island did the Strawhat crew first encounter then captain Smoker ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Whiskey Peak",
	      "Logue Town",
	      "Jaya",
	      "Skypeia"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#26394d",
	    "answer": 1
	  }
	],
	"usopp": [
	  {
	    "id": "9a624b54-100d-4e2f-84eb-22f31ad01208",
	    "question": "On which island did Usopp train during the two year timeskip ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Sabody Archipelago",
	      "Amazon Lily",
	      "Boin Archipelago",
	      "Thriller Bark"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#beb2a3",
	    "answer": 2
	  }
	],
	"whitebeard": [
	  {
	    "id": "e5801aa8-b056-43dc-a366-5109c9a229de",
	    "question": "What is the name of Whitebeard's devil fruit ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Gura Gura no Mi",
	      "Goro Goro no Mi",
	      "Giri Giri no Mi",
	      "Garu Garu no Mi"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#5d384d",
	    "answer": 3
	  }
	],
	"zoro": [
	  {
	    "id": "fb6d4223-4fc6-4b5d-bfbf-cb72bbeb02d8",
	    "question": "What sword did Zoro inherit from his fallen friend Kuina ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Yubashiri",
	      "Wado Ichimonji",
	      "Sandai Kitetsu",
	      "Shisui"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#67876a",
	    "answer": 1
	  }
	]
      },
      "medium": {
	"ace": [
	  {
	    "id": "eb70553a-cef9-4385-bc1f-48d19f681194",
	    "question": "How old was Portgas D. Ace when he became the second division commander of the Whitebeard Pirates ?",
	    "options": [
	      "17 years old",
	      "20 years old",
	      "24 years old",
	      "25 years old"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#78533a",
	    "answer": 1
	  }
	],
	"brook": [
	  {
	    "id": "df9ae3fd-67f6-42a3-abea-9ae255f649e1",
	    "question": "Why caused the demise of Brooks former crew ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Apprehension followed by execution of the entire crew by the Navy",
	      "Attack by sea kings while sailing thorugh the Calm Belt",
	      "The spread of an incurable disease",
	      "Attack by the Roger Pirates"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#695351",
	    "answer": 2
	  }
	]
      },
      "hard": {
	"ace": [
	  {
	    "id": "97442e59-1d41-44c0-ac09-bb0cb3a56e16",
	    "question": "In what One Piece manga chapter did Portgas D. Ace make his debut ?",
	    "options": [
	      "Chapter 152 - Full Moon",
	      "Chapter 153 - To Arabasta",
	      "Chapter 154 - Hiriluk's Sakura",
	      "Chapter 155 - Pirate Sir Crocodile"
	    ],
	    "contributor": "monotonical21@gmail.com",
	    "color": "#78533a",
	    "answer": 2 
	  }
	]
      }
    }
  }
}
